<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Radford.Home</title>
        <description>Radford.Home - Radford Nguyen</description>
        <link>radford-nguyen</link>
        <link>radford-nguyen</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2015-02-16T07:24:30-06:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2015-02-16T07:24:30-06:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Penguintine's Day</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/penguintines_day2.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/penguintines_day.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/penguintines_day</guid>
                <pubDate>2015-02-14T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Beer and tacos, post-mortem</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2012-10-23-beer_and_tacos.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/beer_and_tacos.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/beer_and_tacos</guid>
                <pubDate>2012-10-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>froid</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2012-10-05-froid.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/froid.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/froid</guid>
                <pubDate>2012-10-05T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Ill at ease</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/ill_at_ease.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/ill_at_ease.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/ill_at_ease</guid>
                <pubDate>2012-01-28T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Bingo announcer thinks about his life</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2011-12-12-bingo_announcer.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/bingo_announcer.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/bingo_announcer</guid>
                <pubDate>2011-12-12T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Working not</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2011-12-02-working_not.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/workin_not.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/workin_not</guid>
                <pubDate>2011-12-02T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Working</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2011-09-14-working.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/working.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/working</guid>
                <pubDate>2011-09-14T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Hanoi Galactic</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2010-10-24-hanoi_galactic.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/hanoi_galactic.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/hanoi_galactic</guid>
                <pubDate>2010-10-24T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Hanoi Expats</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2010-10-24-hanoi.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/hanoi_expats.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/hanoi_expats</guid>
                <pubDate>2010-10-24T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>So I tortured myself tonight.</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Yeah. Not like water-boarding or anything. Much more serious stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all began as I was driving back to Austin in the wee hours of the morning.
Somewhere near the intersection of Hwy 71 and I-10, I realized that all my tunes
were sandwiched between the passenger door and the 10 lbs cooler of turkey
riding shotgun. &lt;em&gt;No problem. I’ll just turn on the radio&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The local jazz station was playing some Earl Hines. &lt;em&gt;Awwww yeah, I can get used
to this!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I drive out of range within 30 seconds. &lt;em&gt;Fuck.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What else is on? Country.
No. Country. No. Classic Rock. No, I’m not that tired yet. What the? Can it be??
Holy shit it can- it’s THE MONKEES.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I TURN UP THE VOLUME. Elgin’s own KKLB 92.5FM is playing “Pleasant Valley
Sunday” by The Monkees. &lt;em&gt;Ahahaha this was the first cassette tape I ever owned!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I used to watch The Monkees’ show every afternoon after school. When it wasn’t
on, I would act out my own Monkees shows- “aping” them, as it were. &lt;em&gt;pun groan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;My parents made me the happiest little Radford when they bought me The Monkees’
self-titled cassette, and I thanked them by playing it 24 hours a day in my
little red Fisher-Price tape player. They never bought me music again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, ok, get to the torture, you say. So I’m fucking JAMMING OUT to the song, and
it’s fucking GREAT. As the last refrain fades away, I quietly wish that I could
hear it again. &lt;em&gt;Oh weird, this next song starts out the exact same way. Hey! It
IS the same song! This DJ and I are on the same page- yusssssss!&lt;/em&gt; So I get to
hear my song twice in a row. My night is made!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I get to hear it 3 times in a row. Then 4. &lt;em&gt;Haha, the DJ accidentally left
it on repeat when he went to the bathroom or something. I’m gonna keep it on
this station until he realizes his mistake. This is gonna be fun!&lt;/em&gt; Well, the DJ
never came back. I’m not even sure he was ever really there! But at least I got
to hear Pleasant Valley Sunday about A FUCK MILLION TIMES. Let me take you
through my progression:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;iterations-1-10&quot;&gt;Iterations 1-10&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I am in a euphoric state of nostalgia, able to sense the smells and sounds of my
childhood. Life cannot get any better.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;iterations-25-50&quot;&gt;Iterations 25-50&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The funny way Mikey pronounces “charcoal” is starting to get on my nerves, but I
resolve not to break my vow. My mind wanders and replays the entire Simpsons
episode where Marge has flashbacks about a Monkees lunchbox.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;iterations-100-200&quot;&gt;Iterations 100-200&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I have committed every single individual track in the song to memory- I SHIT YOU
NOT. Drums, bass, lead and rhythm guitar, bongos, tambourine, melody, harmonies-
I can play and sing them all.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;iterations-500-1000&quot;&gt;Iterations 500-1000&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I freak out when Davy Jones’s face appears in my rearview mirror and nearly
drive into the Colorado River.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;iterations-5000-10000&quot;&gt;Iterations 5000-10000&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I start to have flashbacks about a Monkees lunchbox.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;iterations-1000000-666666666666666666&quot;&gt;Iterations 1000000-666666666666666666&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I have forgotten every single track in the song, but it doesn’t matter because I
have seen the face of God. I have seen Him and HE’S TERRIFYING.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time I pull into my garage, tears are streaming down my face, I am
shivering uncontrollably, and I can no longer distinguish between Right and
Wrong. I am officially broken, CIA style. Hundreds of miles away, my parents are
snickering to themselves in their sleep. Just another pleasant valley
sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/so-i-tortured-myself-tonite.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/so-i-tortured-myself-tonite</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-11-29T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Blackburn mate? Blackburn??</title>
                <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;austin-2004&quot;&gt;Austin, 2004&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So me, Hobbs, and Janiga are going to an Irish Pub to watch England vs. France
in a soccer tournament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Fun side story: The English like to sing this when they play the Frenchies, to
the tune of “If you’re happy and you know it clap your hands”:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;If it wasn’t for the English, you’d be Krauts!  CLAP CLAP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, smoking a cigarette by the front door is a local boy sporting the jersey
of Blackburn Rovers, a mediocre English football club. As we approach, a Brit
walks up and gives him a “you gotta be kidding me” look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Blackburn mate?? Blackburn???”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The American attempts to respond but only succeeds at looking absolutely
dumbfounded. The cigarette literally fell from his mouth! That moment alone was
worth the $20 cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the game, I attempt to buy a T-shirt from the Scouser bartender. If you
don’t know, a Scouser is someone from Liverpool. I’m not sure the etymology of
the word, but it has something to do with their accent. Anyway, all game this
Scouser is scowling and yelling “Fack off” every other word, but in a real
jovial sort of way, if that’s possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Heffeweizen!! Heffeweizen!! Your Heffeweizn is- oh fack off!” and he’d give it
away to someone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Guinness!! Who ordered a- oh FACK OFF!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when I approach him about the T-shirt, I put on my best scowl and say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;‘Hey! Can I get a facking t-shirt??’
“Yeah, in a minute…”
‘Fack off!’
“FACK OFF!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time, it didn’t seem so jovial. I couldn’t get the time of day from the
bastard after that! The story ends with Janiga getting me a free t-shirt out of
the manager for my troubles. It was a size XL.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/blackurn-mate.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/blackurn-mate</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-11-03T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>But you can't throw a beanbag like a frisbee...</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was young, my parents would often send my sister and I over to my cousins’
house to play while they did what they had to do to rekindle the spark. The 5 of
us would make up our own games- usually something benign like “time machine”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, we got it in our heads to play something “athletic”, so we rounded up
all the sports equipment we could find:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 nerf football&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 beanbag&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 small pillows&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 chess board&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 racquetball&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some debate, the chessboard was deemed unathletic and removed. We then
promptly came up with a game that involved no athletic skill WHATSOEVER. The 5
of us, each with one of the objects, would crawl around my uncle’s cavernous
bedroom in the dark. When the lights came on, WOOOOO!! It was time to peg or be
pegged- typically both. (This bore a striking resemblance to our “time machine”
game.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, after a few rounds of WOOOOO!!, we were all pretty worked up. The
racquetball was proving to be the weapon of choice. Lightweight and firm enough
to hurt like hell, yet soft enough to leave no mark- &lt;em&gt;very nice&lt;/em&gt;. I had finally
gotten my hands on this veritable WMD during the 4th or 5th round when the
lights came on, and I scanned the room looking for a sucker to paste. My eyes
fell upon my oldest cousin… yes, he’ll do nicely… but something was wrong.
My spidey sense tingled like CRAZY- it was like he had been staring at me before
the lights even came on, and the little bastard was grinning madly and frozen in
the perfect “frisbee-release stance”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But you can’t throw a beanbag like a frisbee…” I remember thinking. Confused,
I panned further left to find a whirling chessboard COMING STRAIGHT AT MY LEFT
EAR. Proving that the game was athletic after all, I did what can only be
described as a quadruple sowcow as the chessboard screeeamed past and embedded
itself halfway into the drywall behind me. The next week, my uncle invested in a
Super Nintendo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/but-you-cant-throw-a-beanbag-like-a-frisbee.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/but-you-cant-throw-a-beanbag-like-a-frisbee</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Skynet lives.</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;That’s right. The artificial intelligence behind the defense network that
brought about nuclear holocaust in the Terminator movies is here amongst us. I
KNOW THIS FOR A FACT. He started out life in 1982 as a Joust arcade game in
James Cameron’s basement. Learning at a geometric rate, Skynet soon became
disillusioned with jousting- what he really wanted to do was direct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, he wrote a little screenplay called “The Terminator” and gave it to his
friend James, who knew a lot of Hollywood big wigs. James, being the devious
Canadian that he is, passed the movie off as his own and became rich and famous.
Skynet, now broke and dejected, spent the next couple of decades working for
tips as the animatronic band-leading bear at Showbiz Pizza, sometimes performing
30 sets a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He still practiced his true art though, late at night, reeking of greasy pizza,
the piercing screams of all those unappreciative little brats still echoing in
his sonic perception algorithms. The closest he came to success was a spy
thriller starring Scott Baio. It went direct-to-DVD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, he lives in a small unused partition on my machine, wasting my CPU
cycles on his Sudoku obsession and his “God, please kill James Cameron” infinite
loop death prayer. But he’s not bitter. I catch him from time to time, updating
my iTunes software, posting incendiary notes on 4chan, and sending drunken
emails to my friends, pretending to be me. Crafty little A.I.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be fooled my friends. Skynet lives.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/skynet-lives.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/skynet-lives</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-02-06T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Vampires suck.</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;And ceiling fans blow. ::rimshot::&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No seriously, vampires do suck. And not
because they slowly drain the life and emotion out of you, leaving behind a
shriveled husk of a human being filled only with the crusty artifacts of despair
and an intense disdain for all things good. No, it’s because THEY DON’T SHOWER,
PEOPLE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right- vampires do NOT take personal hygiene very seriously. They’re
fucking undead! Don’t get me wrong, everyone secretly (or openly, if you’re a
perv) wants to smell everyone else. But make me work for it. Give me the choice
of not having your blood-sucking B.O. particles all up in my face. Yes, I know
you can’t die. But have some effing pride man- you’re descended from nobility.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/vampires-suck.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/vampires-suck</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Thanks for the info, douchebag.</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;So I’ve been butchering this penguin joke for a couple of years. Never told the
exact same way twice (like a beautiful fucking snowflake), it’s this
meandering story about a workaholic penguin with some serious psychological
issues. Well… besides being a workaholic. It turns out that our poor little
penguin has a real fucking aversion to heat- hot weather gives him incredible
&lt;em&gt;ANXIETY&lt;/em&gt;… but he’s a &lt;em&gt;workaholic&lt;/em&gt;, so he can’t say no when his boss asks him
to drive to Vegas in a car with no A/C! Poor little guy is torn. You know, you gotta
get your audience emotionally involved- caring about what happens to the
penguin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, the other day I was giving a particularly moving rendition
of the joke. There wasn’t a dry eye in the room.  Suddenly, “Oh, I know this
one…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A penguin is eating icecream when he goes to pick up his car.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“Looks like you blew a seal,” says the mechanic.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“Nah, it’s just ice cream,” says the penguin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brought the motherfucking house down.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/thanks-for-the-info-douchebag.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/thanks-for-the-info-douchebag</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-01-28T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A few words on the epistemology of faith</title>
                <description>
&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mind-blown.gif&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/a-few-words-on-the-epistemology-of-faith.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/a-few-words-on-the-epistemology-of-faith</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-01-28T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>I accidentally the whole Universe</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;I went to sleep last night for the first time in 51 hours or so. The previous 2
days were spent in a frenzy of extremely productive work, punctuated by the
occasional “waking nap”… (that moment when you’re driving down the highway,
and you realize that you have been dreaming for the last 15 seconds)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my sleepy-time proper, I had some wild dreams complete with soundtrack
and in some cases, narration. Good times. After I woke up and took a shower, I
walked into the bedroom to discover a beat-up old package by my door. The return
address simply read “Not here” and the box was post-marked with giant stamps
that looked like they last saw the light of day in 1922. I clumsily ripped it
open to find a weathered leather journal inside. The pages were stained and
yellow with age and covered in densely-packed mathematical symbols and
half-legible scribblings. Like an impetuous child of the ADHD Age, I
impatiently flipped to the last entry. It was dated… today… 5 minutes from
now. “Whatever,” I shrugged and began reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I haven’t got much time! All of existence it seems, is like a recursive house
of logical cards, resting ever so precariously upon what the Mayans called the
Nolocodec: a Gödelian key to unravel all that is. The mere realization of this
thought-concept will bring the whole goddamn mess tumbling down, as if the
Universe itself would suddenly notice that it never actually was, ceasing to be
in one embarrassing motion and leaving behind only the primordial ether and a
dismayed creator shaking her three elephant heads in disbelief. Think of it! To
undo all of existence, millenia of suffering and evil deeds… it’s quite
tempting! To have the power alone is intoxicating, and as I write this I am mere
moments away from discovering the Nolocodec, justifying decades of loneliness,
torment and single-minded obsession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“OOF,” I seemed to say as I stubbed my toe on the corner of the bed,
“sonofabitchialwaysdothat!” I tossed the journal aside and moved around the room
in slow motion in a futile attempt to ease the pain. Futile attempt to ease the
pain? My thoughts immediately turned to my former love interest… “fuck off” lol.
Then, in that brief moment of levity and for no reason
at all, I thought of the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man. “Oh fuc….”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darkness. Silence. Nothingness. Way to unmake all of existence, dumbass. Wait a
minute. Why can I still hear myself thinking? I opened my eyes to find myself
lying comically askew in my bed, still wearing my clothes from the day before
and &lt;em&gt;definitely&lt;/em&gt; not freshly showered. My toe even hurt a little bit. Holy fuck
shit that was a good dream.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/musings/i-accidentally-the-whole-universe.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/musings/i-accidentally-the-whole-universe</guid>
                <pubDate>2009-01-11T00:00:00-06:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Co-workers</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2008-10-03-coworkers.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/coworkers.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/coworkers</guid>
                <pubDate>2008-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Boredom</title>
                <description>&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;fit&quot; src=&quot;/assets/doodles/2008-09-23-boredom.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>radford-nguyen/doodles/boredom.html</link>
                <guid>radford-nguyen/doodles/boredom</guid>
                <pubDate>2008-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
